The first message is don't call yourself a free people, a free person, if you can't make changes, if you can't stop a genocide that is going, still ongoing since the first day.
We are so close to be a hundred days of murdering and genocide.
So don't you call yourself a free person if you can't stop someone to kill someone else.
Because what I witness here that all the world is ruled by a people that no one in the whole world can say no to them or they can't stop them.
So nobody shall call himself a free person if he's watching another people, another human being getting murdered in front of him.
A live show by a young photographer who is just filming to show the world that he can't stop this.
People call Mautaz like a hero, a sober hero. Mautaz didn't choose this. Mautaz didn't want this.
But I don't want you to justify what is happening or to forget about what is happening by calling someone a sober hero and forget the people who are under like tons of rubble.
And they died there by a missile. Maybe you shared with your taxes to or to give it to the occupation.
So let's go.